http://www.insideride.com/privacy

Qubo Calibration/
Ride your hardest workouts Inside with E-Motion Rollers.
Qubo Calibration/
At Inside Ride, Inc., we are committed to protecting your privacy. The following statement describes the information gathering and usage practices of Inside Ride, Inc.
1. Inside Ride, Inc. will not share, rent or sell your personal information to any non-affiliated organization or company without your consent. However, we may disclose your personal information under limited circumstances if we conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Inside Ride, Inc., its customers or the public.
2. When you register, place an order or provide your personal information to us for any other business purpose, we may collect your name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information. We may also request additional information. We use this information to process your requests and to communicate with you about your orders. From time to time, we may use your name and contact information to notify you of changes to the web site, new releases, special offers and events we think you'll find valuable. To prevent receiving this information via any medium, please send an email to info@insideride.com or a postcard with all the names, addresses and emails you'd like removed from our mailing list to Inside Ride, Inc., Inc, PO Box 1207, North Plains, OR 97133.
3. All of the customer data we collect is stored on a secured server to protect against unauthorized access.
4. Inside Ride, Inc. will track visits to the pages and links on our websites so we can make decisions about the design and usage of the website. While we may choose to share aggregate information on consumer behavior to third parties, none of these statistics contain personally identifying information.
5. Our websites use cookies to identify our registered members when they return to the site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide special features such as storing items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to prevent that by making a change to the browser options. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.
6. By using our website, you consent to the policies described in this privacy statement. The provisions of this policy are subject to change. Inside Ride, Inc. will post changes to this privacy policy on this page.
Buy/
Features/
Support/
Qubo Calibration/
Inside Ride
E-Motion Rollers use our patented FREE MOTION technology, innovative design, and precision manufacturing to provide a more natural and satisfying ride than any other bicycle rollers or trainer.  You get to ride your bicycle like you are on the road. E-Motion Rollers are now available with Smart Resistance so you can use your favorite training apps like Sufferfest, Zwift, and Trainer Road for a virtual cycling experience.
Designed and manufactured in the USA.
Available for purchase online for customers in the USA and CANADA.
.
